Guide to the Rice University KTRU Radio records, 1962-2018 UA 011
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Audio recordings, 1968-2007, 59004
  - Sub-Series: 1977/1978, 59243
    - To the Point - Robert Sterling, 1977-10-26; wrc06668 (Box 8)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Phil Konstantin talks with Robert Sterling about the Jesse H. Jones School of Business Administration and business ethics. We deleted repeated outro music at the end of the recording. Speakers: Robert Sterlin, Phil Konstantin
    - To the Point - William Howell, 1977-11-01; wrc06669 (Box 8)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. William Howell about the psychology of energy conservation. Speakers: William Howell, Lee Hochberg
    - Radio Plays, 1977-11-05; wrc06625; 59294 (Box 8)
      Contents include: The Rice Players and KTRU present two radio plays: "The Last Question" by Isaac Asimov and "Artist Descending a Staircase" by Tom Stoppard. Plays performed in Lyle's in the basement of Lovett College. Speakers: Carman Rodriguez, Mark Brennan, Peter Redding, Paul Todd, Mary Beth Lapis, Liz Israel, Karen Braitmayer, Roberta Witt, Paul Todd, Steve Ortego, Tom Moe, John Mark Bouler, Scott McDonald, Scott Froehlich, James Guenther, Margaret Elsea
    - To the Point - James Blackburn, 1977-11-07; wrc06670 (Box 8)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with James Blackburn about land use proposals. Speakers: James Blackburn, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Paul Cloutier, 1977-11-10; wrc06671 (Box 8)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Paul Cloutier about the future of science. Speakers: Paul Cloutier, Lee Hochberg
    - Up in the Air - Earl Butz, 1977-11-14; wrc06626; 59290 (Box 8)
    - State of the University, 1977-11-14; wrc06627; 59266 (Box 8)
      Contents include: Norman Hackerman gives his yearly "State of the University" address and answers questions. He discusses faculty retention, government-controlled higher education vs. private higher education, women's sports, Title IX, Fondren Library, Southwest Conference participation, tuition, how Rice supplements the cost of a student's education, Brown Foundation challenge, co-ed colleges, overcrowding, Shepherd School of Music, Howard Hughes will litigation, current building construction. Abruptly ends. Speaker: Norman Hackerman
    - To the Point - John Clark, 1977-11-14; wrc06672 (Box 8)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Irene Walker talks with Dr. John Clark about the artificial heart. Speaker: John Clark, Irene Walker
    - To the Point - Dr. Joyce Brothers, 1977-11-16; wrc06673 (Box 8)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Joyce Brothers about the psychology of fragrance and relationships. Speakers: Dr. Joyce Brothers, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Fred von der Mehden, 1977-11-21; wrc06674 (Box 8)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Phil Konstantin talks with Dr. Fred von der Mehden about political violence. Speakers: Fred von der Mehden, Phil Konstantin
    - To the Point - Andrei Amalrik, 1977-11-29; wrc06675 (Box 8)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Andrei Amalrik about his life in Russia as a dissident. Dr. Constantine Ushinsky serves as an interpreter. Speakers: Andrei Amalrik, Lee Hochberg, Constantine Ushinsky
    - To the Point - Charles Doran, 1977-11-30; wrc06676 (Box 8)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Charles Doran about Anwar Sadat's visit to Israel. Speakers: Charles Doran, Lee Hochberg
    - College Bowl matches, 1977-11; wrc07322 (Box 8)
      Contents include: Scott Hochberg moderates college bowls matches at Rice University. The recorder was left on during breaks between rounds and at the end of the recording. We deleted this extraneous audio. Speakers: Scott Hochberg, Wes Parsons, Norby Foss, Paul Todd
    - Houston election coverage, 1977-11; wrc06628; 59246 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Houston city election coverage from various KTRU DJs and correspondents. We have deleted radio music throughout this recording. Speakers: Larry Fossi, Jim McConn, David Zumwalt, Lee Hochberg, Patti Bellis, Stan Barber, David Weiss
    - To the Point - Baine Kerr, 1977-12-02; wrc06677 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Phil Konstantin talks with Baine Kerr, President of Pennzoil, about the oil industry and consumer issues. Speakers: Baine Kerr, Phil Konstantin
    - To the Point - Rice Chorale Christmas Music, 1977-12-08; wrc06678 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Rice Chorale and Chamber Singers perform Christmas music. Performers: Rice Chorale
    - To the Point - Stephen Klineberg, 1977-12-14; wrc06679 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Stephen Klineberg about the issue of abortion. Speakers: Stephen Klineberg, Lee Hochberg
    - George Clinton interview, 1977; wrc07939 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Bruce Kessler talks to George Clinton about recording, cancelled show in Houston, touring, Alice Cooper and KISS comparisons, Parliament and Funkadelic, Eddie Hazel, concert night performances, and his new work. Speakers: George Clinton, Bruce Kessler, Eric Sisson
    - Arbuckle Flat - Victor Viglino, 1977-1978; wrc07938 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "Arbuckle Flat," Victor Viglino plays classical music and talks with Trip Doss. This recordings has poor sound quality. Speakers: Victor Viglino, Trip Doss
    - News Master 5, 1977-1978; wrc06629; 59244 (Box 9)
      Contents include: (00:01) Rumor - Jones and Will Rice College becoming co-ed; (01:02) Rice Recycling Center building new facility; (02:11) Cathy Langford on Honor Council faculty representative; (02:59) Charles, Prince of Wales visit to Houston. Speakers: Stan Barber, Cathy Langford, Charles, Prince of Wales, Fred Hofheinz
    - To the Point - Herb Ward, 1978-01-11; wrc06680 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Herb Ward about solar energy. Speakers: Herb Ward, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Alex Dessler, 1978-01-18; wrc06681 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Alex Dessler about space colonies. Speakers: Alex Dessler, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - John Freeman, 1978-01-25; wrc06682 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. John Freeman about solar satellite program. Speakers: John Freeman, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Joseph Cooper, 1978-01-26; wrc06683 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Joseph Cooper about the U.S. House of Representatives and governmental ethics. Speakers: Joseph Cooper, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Robert Dix, 1978-02-03; wrc06684 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Robert Dix about what the U.S. should do with Panama Canal and the treaties. Speakers: Robert Dix, Lee Hochberg
    - Leo Kottke interview, 1978-02-06; wrc06632; 59298 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Leo Kottke's music is interwoven with interview clips. He discusses his arrest in Bonn, Germany, views on punk, Nick Lowe, his albums, producing, vocal vs. instrumental music, Chrysalis and performing. Speakers: Leo Kottke, David John Scribner
    - To the Point - Hugh Sanborn, 1978-02-15; wrc06685 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Hugh Sanborn about Rice University students working at Casa de Amigos, a drug rehabilitation center. Speakers: Hugh Sanborn, Lee Hochberg
    - Arbuckle Flat - Don Sanders, 1978-02-20; wrc06630; 59299 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Don Sanders on the "Arbuckle Flat" radio program. In the beginning, this recording is very poor. Speakers: Don Sanders, Trip Voss
    - To the Point - Donald Huddle, 1978-02-20; wrc06686 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Donald Huddle about undocumented immigrants and the Simopson-Rodino bill. Speakers: Donald Huddle, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Edgar Edwards, 1978-02-22; wrc06687 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Edgar Edwards about issues in Ethiopia. Speakers: Edgar Edwards, Lee Hochberg
    - Backstage Interview - Edgar Winter, 1978-02-22; wrc07941 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "Backstage Interview," Bruce Kessler talks to Edgar Winter about the Trash Band, other project he would like to explore, Houston music venues, philosophy of making music, producing, musical beginnings, and marketable music. Speakers: Stan Barber, Bruce Kessler, Edgar Winter
    - Student Association elections, 1978-02; wrc06631; 59311 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Stan Barber speaks with SA President candidates Marian Barber and Roy Beller. He also speaks to the Rice Thresher editor candidates: David Butler and Steve Sullivan. We have deleted radio music throughout this recording. Speakers: Stan Barber, Marian Barber, Roy Beller, David Butler, Steve Sullivan
    - Backstage Interview - Gordon Lightfoot, 1978-03-06; wrc06633; 59301 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Stan Barber presents an interview of Gordon Lightfoot, which is interwoven with music. Lightfoot discusses how he got started in the business, Pee Wee Charles, his current touring band, his album Endless Wire, and songwriting. Speakers: Stan Barber, Gordon Lightfoot
    - To the Point - Frank Bearden, 1978-03-10; wrc06695 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Frank Bearden about health and heart attacks. Speakers: Frank Bearden, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Walter Isle, 1978-03-16; wrc06696 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Walter Isle about science fiction in the 1970s. Speakers: Walter Isle, Lee Hochberg
    - Arbuckle Flat - Vince Bell, 1978-03-17; wrc06634; 59303 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Vince Bell on the "Arbuckle Flat" radio program. Speakers: Trip Voss, Vince Bell
    - To the Point - Art Few, 1978-03-20; wrc06697 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Art Few about biomass conversion. Speakers: Art Few, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Priscilla Huston, 1978-03-21; wrc06698 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Priscilla Huston about the future of computing. Speakers: Priscilla Huston, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - William Martin, 1978-03-22; wrc06699 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. William Martin about crime and criminals. Speakers: William Martin, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Allen Matusow, 1978-03-28; wrc06700 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Allen Matusow about the 1960s. Speakers: Allen Matusow, Lee Hochberg
    - Horslips interview, 1978-03-30; wrc07937 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Bruce Kessler interviews members of Horslips, Eamon Carr and Jim Lockhart, about the band's origins, creating their unique sound, songwriting, recording, "The Book of Invasions," instrumentation, album artwork, name of the band, acoustic album, playing with other bands, and working with different labels. They also do a station ID. Speakers: Eamon Carr, Jim Lockhart, Bruce Kessler
    - To the Point - Niels Nielsen, 1978-03-30; wrc06701 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Neils Neilsen about Pres. Jimmy Carter and human rights. Speakers: Neils Neilsen, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Peter Rowe, 1978-04-04; wrc06702 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Peter Rowe about city land use planning. Speakers: Peter Rowe, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Vladimir Lyatokho, 1978-04-06; wrc06703 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Vladimir Lyatokho about the relationship between Russia and China. Speakers: Vladimir Lyatokho, Lee Hochberg
    - Backstage Interview - Carlos Alomar, 1978-04-09; wrc06635; 59314 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Bruce Kessler interviews Carlos Alomar rhythm guitarist in David Bowie's touring band and on his albums. Alomar discusses Bowie's current tour, recording Bowie's music, playing Bowie's catalog on tour, his production company, songwriting, his session work, and his work with Iggy Pop. Speakers: Carlos Alomar, Bruce Kessler
    - To the Point - Charles Philpott, 1978-04-17; wrc06704 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Charles Philpott about genetic engineering and cloning. Speakers: Charles Philpott, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Carl Sharpe, 1978-04-19; wrc06705 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Carl Sharpe about mass transit. Speakers: Carl Sharpe, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Bobby May and Marty Froelich, 1978-04-25; wrc06706 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Bobby May and Marty Froelich about the psychology of long distance running. Speakers: Bobby May, Marty Froelich, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - James Arnold, 1978-05-15; wrc06707 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks with James Arnold about "reunion" as an alternative to deprogramming from religious cults. Speakers: James Arnold, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Konstantin Kolenda, 1978-05-19; wrc06708 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks with Dr. Konstantin Kolenda about coping with death and dying. Speakers: Konstantin Kolenda, Scott Hochberg
    - Backstage Interview - John McLaughlin, 1978-05-22; wrc06636; 59300 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Ricky Dyke interviews John McLaughlin. He discusses his audience, revisiting the electric guitar, Shakti and their albums, touring, writing music, jamming with Jimi Hendrix, and opinions on other jazz groups. Speakers: John McLaughlin, Ricky Dyke
    - Backstage Interview - Nick Lowe, 1978-05-24; wrc06202; 59313 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Bruce Kessler interviews Nick Lowe. They discuss the disposability of pop music, music production, songwriting, creating the album Pure Pop for Now People, pub rock and humor, power pop, death of punk, and new wave. Speakers: Nick Lowe, Bruce Kessler
    - To the Point - Paul Cloutier, 1978-05-25; wrc06709 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks with Dr. Paul Cloutier about the sunken USS Hatteras. Speakers: Paul Cloutier, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Scott Harris, 1978-05-30; wrc06710 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks with Dr. Scott Harris about disarmament and the arms race. Speakers: Scott Harris, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Reese Duke, 1978-06-01; wrc06714 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks with Dr. Reese Duke about education in Texas. Speakers: Reese Duke, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Baruch Brody, 1978-06-05; wrc06711 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks with Dr. Baruch Brody about the consumer movement. Speakers: Baruch Brody, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Donald Huddle, 1978-06-06; wrc06712 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks with Dr. Donald Huddle about inflation and the future of the U.S. economy. Speakers: Don Huddle, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Chad Gordon, 1978-06-21; wrc06713 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks with Dr. Chad Gordon about dealing with aged. Speakers: Chad Gordon, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - William Howell, 1978-06-28; wrc06715 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks with Dr. William Howell about the psychology of energy conservation. Speakers: William Howell, Scott Hochberg
    - Nigel Olsson interview, 1978; wrc07935 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Spring 1978, Bruce Kessler talks to Nigel Olsson about his early music career, playing with the Elton John Band, producing, his solo career, and touring. Speakers: Nigel Olsson, Bruce Kessler, Walter Keeler
    - Gary Burton interview, 1978; wrc07940 (Box 9)
      Contents include: A DJ talks to Gary Burton about his influences, former students, audiences around the world, technique, perceptions as a musician, branching out with atypical jazz musicians, stage outfits as costume, and upcoming plans. Speakers: Gary Burton
  - Sub-Series: 1978/1979, 59295
    - Journey interview, 1978-07-02; wrc07944 (Box 9)
      Contents include: Bruce Kessler talks to members of Journey about adding Steve Perry, selecting material, touring, new music, playing with Santana before creating Journey, and national reception and airplay. They do a station ID. We changed the speed of this recording. Speakers: Steve Perry, Neal Schon, Gregg Rolie, Ross Valory, Aynsley Dunbar
    - To the Point - Charlotte Peltier, 1978-07-05; wrc06759 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Charlotte Peltier about beach management. Speakers: Charlotte Peltier, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Joan Boorman, 1978-07-06; wrc06760 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Joan Boorman about bilingual education. Speakers: Joan Boorman, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Curt Michel, 1978-07-20; wrc06761 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Curt Michel about the problems with the Skylab satellite. Speakers: Curt Michel, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Phil Bedient, 1978-07-20; wrc06762 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Phil Bedient about water run-off and pollution. We deleted extraneous audio at the ending. Speakers: Phil Bedient, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Harold Hyman, 1978-07-21; wrc06763 (Box 9)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Austin Bay talks to Dr. Harold Hyman about the Equal Rights Amendment. We deleted extraneous audio at the ending. Speakers: Harold Hyman, Austin Bay
    - To the Point - Ray Alborn, 1978-07-24; wrc06764 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Austin Bay talks to Coach Ray Alborn about Rice Owls football. Speakers: Ray Alborn, Austin Bay
    - To the Point - Kathleen Matthews, 1978-08-17; wrc06765 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Kathleen Matthews about the ethics of genetic research and test tube babies. Speakers: Kathleen Matthews, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Gordon Smith, 1978-09-05; wrc06766 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks with Dr. Gordon Smith about the state of the dollar. Speakers: Gordon Smith, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Paul Harcombe, 1978-09-13; wrc06767 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Paul Harcombe about endangered species. Speakers: Paul Harcombe, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Bonnie Hellums, 1978-09-17; wrc06768 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Austin Bay talks to Bonnie Hellums about sex education. Speakers: Bonnie Hellums, Austin Bay
    - To the Point - Chandler Davidson, 1978-06-19; wrc06758 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Chandler Davidson about the workforce. Speakers: Chandler Davidson, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Scott Harris, 1978-09-26; wrc06769 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Scott Harris about the Middle East peace process. Speakers: Scott Harris, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Father Don Benjamin, 1978-10-03; wrc06770 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Father Don Benjamin about the search for a new pope and the Catholic Church. Speakers: Father Don Benjamin, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Jean Claude De Braemaker, 1978-10-09; wrc06771 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Jean Claude De Braemaker about earthquakes. Speakers: Jean Claude De Braemaker, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Richard Smith, 1978-10-16; wrc06772 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Richard Smith about China. Speakers: Richard Smith, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Richard Butler, 1978-10-23; wrc06773 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Richard Butler about the recent passage of the energy bill. Speakers: Richard Butler, Lee Hochberg
    - Lovett College Musicale, 1978-10-25; wrc06774; 59310 (Box 10)
      Contents include: The men of Lovett College, as well as Associates, perform for the college.
    - To the Point - Richard Haugh, 1978-10-30; wrc06775 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Richard Haugh about Russia's crackdown on dissidents. Speakers: Richard Haugh, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - John Newport, 1978-11-06; wrc06776 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. John Newport about religion and its role in futurology. Speakers: John Newport, Lee Hochberg
    - Arbuckle Flat - Monica McNeil and Jean Kilbourn, 1978-11-09; 59312 (Box 10)
      Contents include: Monica McNeil and Jean Kilbourn perform on the "Arbuckle Flat" radio program. Speakers: Mary Kay Zuravleff, Monica McNeil, Jean Kilbourn
    - To the Point - Gilbert Cuthbertson, 1978-11-13; wrc06778 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Gilbert Cuthbertson about Gov. Bill Clemmons and Texas political myths. Speakers: Gilbert Cuthbertson, Lee Hochberg
    - Justice Arthur Goldberg speech, 1978-11-14; wrc07993 (Box 10)
      Contents include: Justice Arthur Goldberg speaks at Rice University about the U.S. Constitution and its amendments, freedom of religion, no national church, freedom of religion in Communist countries, being entitled to dignity, jobs, and the Helsinki accord. Speakers: Arthur Goldberg, Niels Nielsen
    - David Butler - Calendar Telescope, 1978-11-19-1978-12-05; wrc06779; 59302 (Box 10)
      Contents include: David Butler reports on all events on campus, as well as weather, for the dates 11-19, 11-20, 12-01, 12-02, 12-04, and 12-05. He also does multiple takes. In the middle of the recording. Because of recording issues, we have altered this recording. Speaker: David Butler
    - To the Point - John Newport, 1978-11-28; wrc06780 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. John Newport about the Peoples Temple, Jonestown massacre, Jim Jones, and cults. Speakers: John Newport, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Eva Lee, 1978-11-29; wrc06781 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Eva Lee about women in sports. Speakers: Eva Lee, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Konstantin Kolenda, 1978-12-04; wrc06782 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Konstantin Kolenda about humanism and religion. Speakers: Konstantin Kolenda, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Edward Williams, 1978-12-06; wrc06783 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Edward Williams about small business owners. Speakers: Edward Williams, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Mary Rawlinson, 1978-12-08; wrc06784 (Box 10)
    - To the Point - Diana Rathjen, 1978-12-11; wrc06785 (Box 10)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Lee Hochberg talks with Dr. Diana Rathjen about the importance of touch and communication in relationships. Speakers: Diana Rathjen, Lee Hochberg
    - To the Point - Scott Harris, 1978-12-12; wrc06786 (Box 10)